NIKHIL SAXENA | FULL STACK DEVELOPER

H-15 SDM Colony Sikandarabad Bulandshahr 203205 +91 955-759-2404 nikhilsaxena694@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Motivated junior web developer looking for a role as a full-stack web developer. Passionate about building first-class web applications. Developed a "CRM& DHCLSC.org" based web application & work on "Point of sale" software.

	AREAS OF EXPERTISE	
✓ HTML	✓ jQuery	
✓ CSS	✓ C#	
✓ JavaScript	✓ Asp.Net MVC	
Bootstrap	✓ SQL Server	
	PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE	

MaveSys Infotech Pvt Ltd

Full Stack Web Developer | 09 September, 2022 - Present

- Oversee and maintain web services and websites.
- Work on POS software & create CRM & DHCLSC.org web applications as per the client's requirements.
- Collaborate with senior developers to update the website and create new features.
- Develop new user-facing features, determine the structure and design of web pages, and build reusable codes and various makeup languages to create the web pages.

WEBINK DIGITAL

Web Developer Intern| Feb 2022-Aug 2022

- Built and maintained websites for clients through various online platforms.
- Created and tested applications for websites.
- Analyze the requirements, gathered information, and performed research.

PROJECT

Title:

Online MYTRVLDIARY Website using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJS Languages, and API.

Summary:-

The purpose of making a website is to make a traveling management system easier so that customers can be served under a very efficient management a system that will provide all kinds of services book a complete travel package, easy to contact.

Link:-

https://nikhilsaxena16.github.io/TRAVEL_DIARIES/

EDUCATION

May-Dec 2021 | CETPA INFOTECH PVT LTD
MERN STACK DEVELOPER DIPLOMA

2017-2020 | Kalinga UniversityBACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATION

2014-2017 | Kalinga University Diploma in Civil Engineering

2014 | UP Board

12th

2012 | UP Board

10th

CERTIFICATES

- HackerRank Gold Badge for 10 Days of JavaScript
- Frontend development libraries by freecodecamp
- Back End Development and APIs Responsive Web Design by Sololearn
- jQuery by Sololearn
- HTML by Sololearn
- CSS by Sololearn